creoworx.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy - CreoWorx

**Your privacy is critically important to us at CreoWorx. We do not ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. Plus, we’ll never share or sell it.**

Like most website operators, CreowWorx collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how CreoWorx’s visitors use its website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

CreoWorx also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs.

CreoWorx only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

For your security, we do not save your credit card on our site.

### Personal Information

Certain visitors to CreoWorx choose to interact with CreoWorx in ways that require CreoWorx to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that CreoWorx gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.

Those who engage in transactions with CreoWorx – by purchasing our Theme Setup service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions.

In each case, CreoWorx collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with CreoWorx. CreoWorx does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Again, we do not store your credit card, ever.

### Personal Protection

CreoWorx discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on CreoWorx’s behalf or to provide services available at CreoWorx’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using CreoWorx’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. CreoWorx will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, CreoWorx discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when CreoWorx believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of CreoWorx, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an CreoWorx website and have supplied your email address, CreoWorx may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with CreoWorx and our products.

We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

CreoWorx takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website.

Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website(s), with the drawback that certain facets of our website may not function properly.

### Business Transfers

If CreoWorx, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that CreoWorx goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of CreoWorx may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Advertisements

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer.

This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by CreoWorx and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Changes

CreoWorx reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this agreement. Your continued use of or access to the website following the posting of any changes to this agreement constitutes acceptance of those changes.
